[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", ":", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "If you could choose one partner, who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "I'm looking over, I see people going -- don't do it, don't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "You're Irish descent, but you're Scottish basically, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Six hours a day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Did it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Really, really did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Was it a kind of sense of absolute euphoria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "No, because I look ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "You went to Edinburgh Festival, the famous arts and creative festival in Scotland and basically got wrecked, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "This is a great start to an interview, here you are fat, and now let's talk about the time you were fired.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Edinburgh Festival"], "LOCATION": ["Scotland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "You were actually shackled, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I was shackled, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Was that a wake-up moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "That was a wake up moment, yes, but in truth I had a few of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Do you ever wonder what may have happened if you passed your law degree, if you passed exams, if you'd become a lawyer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Yes, I don't think I would have, I don't think I'd be alive today to be honest, and I don't say that lightly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Did she realize as what you were supposed to be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Yes, she did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Let's go, get up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Why this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "It's the way you introduced the movie is the very same reason I wanted to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "It's a God-fearing bad boy sees the light, parallels?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "As you were filming, were you thinking -- I mean very different story line, but you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I think sometimes you read a script and you don't know why, you just think I connect with this, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "It's a cliche question, but did it make you reassess yourself, your sense of what's important in life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Are you very religious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "I'm -- I was brought up a Catholic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Where are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I'm away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Sam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Can you hear me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Yes, I can hear you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "When you finish scenes like that, how do you unwind after, can you or does it hang with you for a long time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "It hangs with you for awhile, and with this movie, there was very much a cumulative effect, because you know from day one you find yourself playing more and more of these scenes where you're either having some kind of breakdown via your drugs or family pressures.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "ORGAN: -- by what you had to see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Have you asked yourself that question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "What would be the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I mean, I would give anybody free power to do whatever they wanted to if it was a family member of mine, and I myself would do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "So, when did you realize this kind of look that you have was going to turn women wild?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I don't know if I ever worked that out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "I mean, these all just a brand extension, isn't it, all these kinds of stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "But is there -- is there a turning point for that when people start to say what's up with you, then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Does your mother want to see her little boy settle down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Get married, have little Gerards running around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I don't think she wants little Gerards.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "VB", ":", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Have you worked out what your dream woman would be, from all the experience you've had playing the field, have you actually worked out in your head what kind of characteristics and looks the one needs to have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "CD", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I mean, I could give you something, and then walk out of here and see a woman that's absolute opposite and go -- oh, wow, because I don't think there's a definite type.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What kind of personality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I love vivacious, but I love a good heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Good humor attract for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "And fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "If you could choose one partner for a desert island, if I was going to send you there for a year, who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Oh, God, I'm looking over.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "You know, once I talked to Michael -- we used to discuss big issues, including life and death.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Is fame in itself an addictive drug?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Fame in itself is an addictive drug.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "What did you know about his drug consumption?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, Michael only called me when he was totally sober and was off drugs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "What's your understanding about the repercussions of what we're watching here on screen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "It's a common story, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Or was it a bit of an act?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, in a sense, we're all multiple personalities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "What was your understanding of his physical condition through this period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "HOPRA: Well, Piers, I wasn't there at those rehearsals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Are either of you legally allowed to administer Propofol in a private house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I don't think so, and neither a cardiologist or an endocrinologist should administer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Why did no one perform a kind of intervention and just try and get him off this stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "There were a couple of interventions to no avail.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Is that the tenet of this book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Yes, that's the basic idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Any of the top ones?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "LODINOW: Oh, yes, many scientists believe in God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Isn't there a contradiction there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Well, first of all, I don't say that I don't believe in god.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I don't think people are that interested -- I don't think people are really that interested in my personal views.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Do you believe in God?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I believe in a kind of God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Deepak"]}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "And so, you know, if you want to go in that direction, you should ask, like Deepak does, where do those laws come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Let me go to Deepak.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Deepak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "HOPRA: Well, it's the eternal mystery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "What happens to me after I die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "We could be here all day with this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "TO", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Where do you think you go when you die, Leonard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I think when, you know, ashes to ashes, dust to dust.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leonard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "That's the end of Leonard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "You know, I would love to think that it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Deepak?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I think we go back to the infinite consciousness where we emerged from.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]